If we are providing knowledge and experience, we need to structure that. And the last one is support. We all started as novices. Everything we do is an approximation of sophistication. We should expect it to change over time. We have to support that. The support may come in asking people questions, giving them a sheet of paper that has an organizational chart on it or has some guiding images, but we need to support it. Now, the final piece of this, the take-home message from a working memory capacity standpoint is this: what we process, we learn. If we're not processing life, we're not living it. Live life. Thank you. (Applause)
Si on crée des connaissances et de l'expérience on a besoin de les structurer. Et la dernière chose est le soutien. On a tous commencé novices. Tout ce qu'on fait est une approximation de la sophistication. On doit s'attendre à en changer au cours du temps. On doit encourager ça. Le soutien peut venir en posant des questions à quelqu'un, en lui montrant une feuille de papier avec un organigramme ou quelques images directrices, mais on a besoin de soutenir ça. Le dernier point, le message clé du point de vue de la mémoire de travail est ceci : ce que nous traitons, nous l'apprenons. Si on ne traite pas la vie, on ne la vit pas. Vivez la vie. Merci. (Applaudissements)